RG 029, Military Census
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Microfilm, 1917-1918; 1988-089
  - 284900-286589, 1803 exposures; 1548195 (Reel 167)
    Refilmed 284900-284979
  - 286590-288380, 1859 exposures; 1548196 (Reel 168)
  - 288381-290109, 1803 exposures; 1548197 (Reel 169)
  - 290110-291799, 1806 exposures; 1548198 (Reel 170)
  - 291800-293559, 1849 exposures; 1548199 (Reel 171)
  - 293560-295330, 1845 exposures; 1548200 (Reel 172)
  - 295331-297059, 1810 exposures; 1548201 (Reel 173)
  - 297060-298450, 1580 exposures; 1548202 (Reel 174)
  - 298451-300109, 1839 exposures; 1548203 (Reel 175)
  - 300110-301770, 1813 exposures; 1548204 (Reel 176)
  - 301771-303519, 1852 exposures; 1548301 (Reel 177)
  - 303520-305139, 1815 exposures; 1548302 (Reel 178)
  - 305140-306859, 1818 exposures; 1548303 (Reel 179)
  - 306860-308559, 1817 exposures; 1548304 (Reel 180)
  - 308560-310189, 1806 exposures; 1548305 (Reel 181)
  - 310190-311879, 1794 exposures; 1548306 (Reel 182)
  - 311880-313559, 1820 exposures; 1548307 (Reel 183)
  - 313560-315229, 1829 exposures; 1548308 (Reel 184)
  - 315230-316920, 1847 exposures; 1548309 (Reel 185)
  - 316921-318580, 1814 exposures; 1548310 (Reel 186)
  - 318581-319799, 1346 exposures; 1548311 (Reel 187)
  - 319800-321489, 1851 exposures; 1548440 (Reel 188)
  - 321490-323209, 1825 exposures; 1548441 (Reel 189)
  - 323210-324939, 1830 exposures; 1548442 (Reel 190)
  - 324940-326679, 1827 exposures; 1548443 (Reel 191)
  - 326680-328429, 1870 exposures; 1548444 (Reel 192)
  - 328430-330189, 1866 exposures; 1548445 (Reel 193)
  - 330190-331899, 1825 exposures; 1548446 (Reel 194)
  - 3318900-333629, 1849 exposures; 1548447 (Reel 195)
  - 333630-335079, 1593 exposures; 1548448 (Reel 196)
  - 335080-336839, 1879 exposures; 1548449 (Reel 197)
  - 336840-338559, 1821 exposures; 1548450 (Reel 198)
  - 338560-340290, 1809 exposures; 1548511 (Reel 199)
  - 340291-342029, 1861 exposures; 1548512 (Reel 200)
  - 342030-343749, 1816 exposures; 1548513 (Reel 201)
  - 343750-345459, 1811 exposures; 1548514 (Reel 202)
  - 345460-347159, 1809 exposures; 1548515 (Reel 203)
  - 347160-348589, 1577 exposures; 1548516 (Reel 204)
  - 348590-350319, 1867 exposures; 1548517 (Reel 205)
  - 350320-352059, 1871 exposures; 1548518 (Reel 206)
  - 352060-353829, 1866 exposures; 1548646 (Reel 207)
  - 353830-355559, 1857 exposures; 1548647 (Reel 208)
  - 355560-357099, 1641 exposures; 1548648 (Reel 209)
  - 357100-358859, 1864 exposures; 1548649 (Reel 210)
  - 358860-360629, 1863 exposures; 1548650 (Reel 211)
  - 360630-362169, 1666 exposures; 1548651 (Reel 212)
  - 362170-363729, 1858 exposures; 1548652 (Reel 213)
  - 363730-365489, 1870 exposures; 1548653 (Reel 214)
  - 365490-367199, 1863 exposures; 1548654 (Reel 215)
  - 367200-368909, 1862 exposures; 1548655 (Reel 216)
  - 368910-370689, 1871 exposures; 1548816 (Reel 217)
  - 370690-372409, 1853 exposures; 1548817 (Reel 218)
  - 372410-374099, 1842 exposures; 1548818 (Reel 219)
  - 374100-375449, 1461 exposures; 1548819 (Reel 220)
  - 375450-377179, 1870 exposures; 1548820 (Reel 221)
  - 377180-378919, 1876 exposures; 1548821 (Reel 222)
  - 378920-380299, 1517 exposures; 1548822 (Reel 223)
  - 380300-381699, 1633 exposures; 1548985 (Reel 224)
  - 381700-383399, 1880 exposures; 1548986 (Reel 225)
  - 383400-385059, 1842 exposures; 1548987 (Reel 226)
  - 385060-386739, 1847 exposures; 1548988 (Reel 227)
  - 386740-388439, 1857 exposures; 1548989 (Reel 228)
  - 388440-390189, 1866 exposures; 1548990 (Reel 229)
  - 390190-391909, 1954 exposures; 1571224 (Reel 230)
  - 391910-393579, 1850 exposures; 1571225 (Reel 231)
  - 393580-395249, 1860 exposures; 1571226 (Reel 232)
  - 395250-396959, 1866 exposures; 1571227 (Reel 233)
  - 396960-398349, 1604 exposures; 1571228 (Reel 234)
  - 398350-400039, 1851 exposures; 1571229 (Reel 235)
  - 400040-401439, 1618 exposures; 1571242 (Reel 236)
  - 401440-403109, 1861 exposures; 1571243 (Reel 237)
  - 403110-404789, 1861 exposures; 1571244 (Reel 238)
  - 404790-406419, 1866 exposures; 1571245 (Reel 239)
  - 406420-408039, 1861 exposures; 1571246 (Reel 240)
  - 408040-409719, 1867 exposures; 1571247 (Reel 241)
  - 409720-411110, 1615 exposures; 1571629 (Reel 242)
  - 411111-412719, 1841 exposures; 1571630 (Reel 243)
  - 412720-414389, 1848 exposures; 1571631 (Reel 244)
  - 414390-416039, 1841 exposures; 1571632 (Reel 245)
  - 416040-417679, 1848 exposures; 1571633 (Reel 246)
  - 417680-419319, 1863 exposures; 1571634 (Reel 247)
  - 419320-421029, 1865 exposures; 1571916 (Reel 248)
  - 421030-422459, 1616 exposures; 1571917 (Reel 249)
  - 422460-424149, 1864 exposures; 1571918 (Reel 250)
  - 424150-425709, 1800 exposures; 1571919 (Reel 251)
  - 425710-427319, 1853 exposures; 1571920 (Reel 252)
  - 427320-428849, 1811 exposures; 1571921 (Reel 253)
  - 428850-430289, 1604 exposures; 1571999 (Reel 254)
  - 430290-431909, 1881 exposures; 1572000 (Reel 255)
  - 431910-433459, 1870 exposures; 1572001 (Reel 256)
  - 433460-435059, 1888 exposures; 1572002 (Reel 257)
  - 435060-436839, 1874 exposures; 1572003 (Reel 258)
  - 436840-438349, 1857 exposures; 1572004 (Reel 259)
  - 438350-439599, 1479 exposures; 1561542 (Reel 260)
  - 439600-441049, 1688 exposures; 1561543 (Reel 261)
  - 441050-442569, 1744 exposures; 1561544 (Reel 262)
  - 442570-444109, 1750 exposures; 1561545 (Reel 263)
  - 444110-445619, 1708 exposures; 1561546 (Reel 264)
  - 445620-447079, 1696 exposures; 1561547 (Reel 265)
  - 447080-448489, 1626 exposures; 1561735 (Reel 266)
  - 448490-450129, 1872 exposures; 1561736 (Reel 267)
  - 450130-451799, 1866 exposures; 1561737 (Reel 268)
  - 451800-453439, 1869 exposures; 1561738 (Reel 269)
  - 453440-455019, 1852 exposures; 1561739 (Reel 270)
  - 455020-456609, 1908 exposures; 1561740 (Reel 271)
  - 456610-457409, 1014 exposures; 1561713 (Reel 272)
    New film emul. 11390101.
  - 457410-458999, 1874 exposures; 1577516 (Reel 273)
  - 459000-460419, 1619 exposures; 1577828 (Reel 274)
  - 460420-462079, 1870 exposures; 1577829 (Reel 275)
  - 462080-463599, 1873 exposures; 1577830 (Reel 276)
  - 463600-465169, 1831 exposures; 1577831 (Reel 277)
  - 465170-466789, 1868 exposures; 1577832 (Reel 278)
  - 466790-468300, 1961 exposures; 1533560 (Reel 279)
  - 468300-469929, 1880 exposures; 1577834 (Reel 280)
  - 469930-471509, 1796 exposures; 1577957 (Reel 281)
  - 471510-472859, 1568 exposures; 1577958 (Reel 282)
  - 472860-474489, 1834 exposures; 1577959 (Reel 283)
  - 474490-476119, 1833 exposures; 1577960 (Reel 284)
  - 476120-477809, 1895 exposures; 1577961 (Reel 285)
  - 477810-479429, 1831 exposures; 1577962 (Reel 286)
  - 479430-481159, 1877 exposures; 1577963 (Reel 287)
  - 481160-482839, 1871 exposures; 1577964 (Reel 288)
  - 482840-484519, 1881 exposures; 1577965 (Reel 289)
  - 484520-485899, 1627 exposures; 1577966 (Reel 290)
  - 485900-487509, 1830 exposures; 1577967 (Reel 291)
  - 487510-488899, 1633 exposures; 1578953 (Reel 292)
  - 488900-490519, 1872 exposures; 1578954 (Reel 293)
  - 490520-491919, 1717 exposures; 1578955 (Reel 294)
  - 491920-493539, 1856 exposures; 1578956 (Reel 295)
  - 493540-495129, 1869 exposures; 1578957 (Reel 296)
  - 495130-496649, 1825 exposures; 1578958 (Reel 297)
  - 496650-498009, 1621 exposures; 1578985 (Reel 298)
  - 498010-499429, 1811 exposures; 1578986 (Reel 299)
  - 499430-501039, 1873 exposures; 1578987 (Reel 300)
  - 501040-502549, 1812 exposures; 1578988 (Reel 301)
  - 502550-502980, 1399 exposures; 1578989 (Reel 302)
    After sheet 502980 there are some miscellaneous numbered sheets of, "Non-resideents with no information"; and there are some non-numbered sheets of, "Refusals", "Army and Navy blanks from Groton", and "Somers, Connecticut" sheets (may be duplicates).